need4video.com 2014-04-20

# Need4Video Privacy Policy | Need4Video

|   
 |   
|   
|  | 

Need4Video: PRIVACY POLICY

Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used, for what purposes, and how we safeguard your personal information. 

Need4Video respects your individual security and privacy, and protects your personal information. Generally, you are not required to provide any personal information to us. For specific purposes, in case you provide your personal information that is required for registration or fill in installation forms, you will be deemed to have accepted the use of your personal information and agreed that Need4Video uses your personal information for the purposes listed below. 

Need4Video does not distribute or share your personal information with third parties. We will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever. You shall have foreseen and agreed to the occurrence of events when you provide your personal information. 

Information Collected

Need4Video collects information provided by you by the following methods:

**Subscription to Need4Video email newsletter**

Being subscribed to our newsletter, you will receive regular emails containing relevant product information, product upgrade information, special offers and attractive discounts which are not available from other sources. 

You can always unsubscribe from our newsletters at any time you wish simply by following the unsubscribe information contained in the emails.

**Software installation form**

During installation Need4Video reserves the right to request some information from you. After providing this information, you will receive emails relating to upgrade information about Need4Video, special offers and attractive discounts which are not available from other sources. If at any time you wish to unsubscribe from these communications, please follow the unsubscribe information contained in the emails. 

**Order process**

When you place an order, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date will be required. Credit card information is used to complete the transaction. It is encrypted during the ordering process and is deleted as soon as your order is completed. We do not keep or record your credit card number - it is simply passed through to the credit card company to purchase our products. All other personal information is held to help us provide better support and services to you.

Cookies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use cookies, a small text file stored on your computer. Cookies work as your identification card and may record preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

Personal Information

Need4Video collects contact information when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill in a software installation form. This information will be used for administrative and identification purposes only and will not be shared with our partners or third parties. Personal information is only accessed by authorized Need4Video personnel.

We respect your privacy and do not sell or rent our customers' personal information to any outside parties. 

﻿  
  
|   
  |    

**Disclaimer.** Please be aware that Need4Video Software does not work with video files and DVDs with copy protection.

Select language: English | English UK | Deutsch | Italiano | Français | Español | [日本語](http://need4video.jp/) | 中文 | 한국어

© Need4Video Ltd., www.need4video.com. All rights reserved.
